eatmyshorts.net 2011-05-16

# Privacy Policy - Eatmyshorts.com

Eatmyshorts.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site.

Personal Information

This Web site does not request any personal information or collect any information that personally identifies you or allows you to be personally contacted. Since we do not collect any personal information on this Web site, we do not share any personal information with any third parties nor do we use any personal information for any purposes. 

Information Automatically Logged 

Eatmyshorts.com also logs IP addresses for systems administration purposes. IP addresses are logged to track a user’s session. This gives Eatmyshorts.com an idea of which parts of our site users are visiting. We do not link IP addresses to anything personally identifiable. This means that a users session will be tracked, but the user will be anonymous 

Cookies

Cookies, by themselves, cannot be used to find out the identity of any user. Eatmyshorts.com will only store information provided voluntarily, but this information is not personally identifiable. If for some reason you would rather not take advantage of the benefits made possible with cookies, most browsers allow you to reject cookies or to choose which cookies to accept, however doing so will make it impossible for you to log in as a member or use any other advanced functionality of the site that requires cookies (ie: post comments, vote on content, submit new content or have new videos recommended to you based on your previous viewing habits, etc). 

Contacting Eatmyshorts.com

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Eatmyshorts.com, you can contact us here.
